Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on canister as Clinic cutups: Section 1. C/1; Section 2. C/2, C/5, 2 man; Section 3. 7, 7 free], undated (Carton 109)
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on canister as Clinic = Coach Boyce], undated (Carton 109)
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on canister as Peach Bowl Defense], undated (Carton 109)
- Miscellaneous football footage [Peach Bowl coverage], undated (Carton 91)
- Miscellaneous football footage (possibly game footage NC State vs. Clemson) [labeled on canister as Practice, 2 of 2], undated (Carton 109)
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on canister as 36-37], undated (Carton 109)
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on canister as 650-651], undated (Carton 109)
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on cassette as N.C. State Football Photo Essay], undated (Carton 91)
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on cassette as Game day highlights, shot from stadium], undated (Carton 91)
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on cassette as NC State vs. UNC--Chapel Hill, Appalachian State University, Virginia], undated (Carton 110)
- Miscellaneous football footage [NC State vs. Arizona preview (Copper Bowl)], undated (Carton 110)
- Miscellaneous football footage [State practice (Copper Bowl)], undated (Carton 110)
- Miscellaneous football footage [Cooper Bowl practice], undated (Carton 110)
- Miscellaneous football footage [State-Tech], undated (Carton 110)
- Miscellaneous football footage [Peach Bowl #2], undated (Carton 110)
- Miscellaneous football footage [Atlantic Coast Conference], undated (Reel 16)
- Miscellaneous football footage [NCSU Football Pt. 1], undated (Box 111)
- Miscellaneous football footage [NCSU Football Pt. 3], undated (Box 111)
- Miscellaneous football footage [NCSU Football Pt. 4], undated (Box 111)
- 1967 Liberty Bowl - NCSU vs Georgia (color/silent) (Carton 3)
  CD
- Miscellaneous football footage [#3 Shaw and Stults highlights], undated (Box 111)
- Miscellaneous football footage [labeled on reel as "Players"], undated (Box 111)
- Miscellaneous football footage [Player clips, game action], undated (Carton 110)
- Miscellaneous football footage, undated (Reel 18)
- Miscellaneous football footage, undated (Reel 19)
- Miscellaneous football footage, undated (Reel 20)
- Miscellaneous football footage [unlabeled], undates (Box 111)
- Miscellaneous football footage [unlabeled], undated (Box 111)
- Miscellaneous football footage [unlabeled, 4 reels], undated (Carton 110)
- Citadel vs. State, 1938 (Carton 112)
  This film is damaged and cannot be played back without extensive conservation work.
- Duke vs. State, 1942 (Carton 112)
- Duke vs. State, 1937 (Carton 112)
- UNC vs. State, 1st half (Carton 112)
  This film is damaged and cannot be played without extensive conservation work.
- UNC vs. State, 2nd half, 1939 (Carton 112)
- NCSU Football Tape 1, undated (Carton 113)
- NCSU Football Tape 2, undated (Carton 113)
- NCSU Football Tape 3, undated (Carton 113)
- Ted Brown 3:00, undated (Carton 113)
- 100 Years of Wolfpack Football, undated (Carton 113)
- Dr. Jerry Punch Wolfpack Pride, undated (Carton 113)
- Red and White #1, undated (Carton 113)
- Red and White #2, undated (Carton 113)
- Red and White, undated (Carton 113)